Hi, I'm Jana and I'm a nutritionist. I'm a mom of three myself and I also work in
early childhood allergy prevention. My husband and I have hay fever which means
our kids have a higher risk of allergies. Diet is super important for reducing the
risk of allergies. You should start feeding your kids solid foods after they
are seven months old at the latest. My children have always loved eating eggs.
They are a great food for little ones and thanks to their high protein content
are also very good for brain development. There is no need to worry that this will
increase the risk of developing allergies as was often said in the past.
On the contrary, feeding eggs to children at an early age prevents allergies. To
test whether the kids were allergic to egg white, I first applied a little egg
to their skin.
This allowed me to see whether they had an allergic reaction or not. Since this
wasn't the case with my three, we often have delicious scrambled eggs, fried eggs,
etc. for dinner and the kids are super fit and happy.